# KOMAL JADVANI Web Developer

komaljadvani3@gmail.com https://github.com/komal3 562-296-3051 https://www.linkedin.com/in/komaljadvani/

Broadly and deeply knowledgeable in a wide variety of computer languages as well as the principles and techniques of website construction and maintenance. I am highly adept at conveying complex technical information to lay audiences in a clear and understandable manner. This allows me to work with people of all experiences and backgrounds.

## **EXPERIENCE**

Freelancer San Antonio, Texas

Web Developer May 2017-Present

Develop project concepts and maintain optimal workflow. Complete detailed programing and development tasks for front end public and internal websites as well as challenging backs-end server code. Collaborate with designers to create clean interfaces and simple, intuitive interactions and experiences.

General Assembly Austin, Texas

Web Development Immersive Student

Feb 2017 - May 2017

It was a 12 week immersive program where I learned an programming languages, frameworks and technologies. I was given the opportunity to apply all of this new knowledge with in class exercise, building the application individual and in-group environment.

# **QuickStart Business Services**

Alice, Texas

Web Developer

Feb 2016 -Jan 2017

Planning, developing and maintaining the front-end functionality of websites. Contacted clients to obtain information and discuss design options. Complete detailed programming and development tasks for front-end public and internal website as well as back-end code. Used Bootstrap to design a responsive website. Carry out quality assurance tests to discover errors and optimize usability.

# **PROJECTS**

#### **Dine Tunning**

This app helps you find local restaurants. It uses your browser geolocation to find your location and serve you a restaurant list. You can search cuisine and sort the restaurant list results by distance and ratings. This app uses the Yahoo YQL API for restaurant data and Google Maps API to find your zip code according to latitude and longitude obtained from geolocation.

#### **Movie APP**

This app is targeting movie lovers. Users can view a range of different movie related information such as trailers, posters, details, ratings etc. Users can also view movie according to genres. This app uses the TMDb API for movies data and Youtube API for trailer.

### **SKILLS**

- Programming language: C, JavaScript, jQuery, HTML, CSS, PHP, HTML5, CSS3, Python.
- Software Tools: Mat lab, Xilinx ISE, Adobe Photoshop, PHP storm, ATOM.
- Database: SQL, MongoDB
- Framework: Bootstraps 3.1, Node.JS, Express.JS, React.JS, Angular.JS.

### **EDUCATION**

# California State University, Long Beach

Long Beach, CA

(Master of Science in Electrical Engineering)